vidahost.com 2016-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Vidahost

This agreement is made between **Paragon Internet Group Ltd t/a Vidahost** , a limited company registered in England and Wales with company number 7573953 and VAT Registration Number GB 182 1470 21, with the registered office The Shipping Building, Old Vinyl Factory, 252 – 254 Blyth Road, Hayes, Middlesex, England, UB3 1HA. ("Vidahost" which expression shall include all or any of its subsidiaries, agents, successors and assigns), and you the customer ("Customer" which expression shall include its permitted successors and assigns).

#### We take your privacy and security very seriously.

The policies we have in place are to protect your personal information, which we store on our secured servers in the UK. By using this website you consent that all personal data you submit may be processed in the manner and for the purposes described here.

Online transactions are handled through **SSL-secured servers** and sensitive details such as passwords and credit card details are **encrypted** to reduce the risk of fraud. We strongly advise that you use hard-to-guess, unique passwords for your accounts with us to reduce the risk of fraud.

We may collect and process data about you in relation to details of transactions that you carry out through our website. When making a purchase with us we will collect information which includes your name, address, e mail address, phone number and payment information.

When you become a customer you automatically subscribe to our newsletter and we will notify you of special offers and updates to our services in the newsletter. If you prefer to opt out of non service e mails, please let us know during the order process. You can also opt out at any time through our client area.

Information obtained about you will assist us in identifying any accounts you hold with us and will also assist us in improving customer care through reviewing, developing and improving the website and services. We will also use the information to notify you about changes to the website and to send service related announcements.

We may disclose your personal information to any of the following third parties:

  * Any employees, agents or service providers of the Company.
  * Any prospective purchaser of the Company subject to them entering into confidentiality undertakings.
  * Any cardholder who has purchased services on your behalf.
  * Where we are required to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation or to protect the rights, property or safety of the Company and our customers. This includes but is not limited to exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection, credit risk reduction and dispute policies.

The Data Protection Act 1998 gives you the right to access information held about you. Any access request will be subject to an administration fee of [£5/10] to meet our costs in providing the information requested.

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, the data controller is Paragon Internet Group (Company Registration Number 7573953) whose registered office is at Prince Albert House, 20 King Street, Maidenhead, Berkshire, SL6 1DT.

This website contains links to external sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content of any external sites.
